

Ailin Mustafa

Date of Birth: 20th August 1994 Nationality: Romanian

Address: 23A Vanatori, Constanta, Constanta 8000900

Phone Number: +40 721 544 545 Email Address: mustafa.aylin08@gmail.com

Skype ID: ailin.mustafa20

Objective

To find my place in the Hospitality industry, to make a difference for the guests and be sure they get un unforgettable experience.

Background

I am currently a third-year student at American Hotel Academy and with the knowledge and experience I have gained daily, I am making steps towards a future career in one of the many departments this industry has to offer. I worked for a couple of years in different environments that are customer support related and I feel like my personality and enthusiasm are suitable to assist guests with any question or concern they may have. I have finished a foreign language High School with intensive English classes and volunteered ever since. I am a friendly, warm and a fast learning person who can easily adapt in any environment.

Qualifications

Computer programs: Microsoft Office Pack (Word, PowerPoint, Excel);

Industry specific programs: Fidelio, Avalon, Medallion, POS;

Languages: Turkish (Mother Tongue), Romanian (Advanced), English (Advanced), Spanish (Beginner), French (Beginner); German (Beginner);

Driver's License: Category B;

Other skills: adaptability, fast learning, good communication skills, opened minded, punctual, works good in a team, organized, hard worker;

Education

2016- present American Hotel Academy, Brasov, Romania

Bachelor of Arts (Hons) - International Hotel Business Management

2009-2013 "George Calinescu" Theoretical High School, Constanta

Literature and Intensive English

Experience

1st May 2018- Receptionist 1st October 2018 Nvota Hotel a

Nyota Hotel and Conference Center, Mamaia, Romania

Duties: 12-hour shifts, day and night, followed by two free days; Check-in and Check-out of guests, constant communication between the hotel and the partner club, Loft Mamaia as our guests received free access to the club's private beach; the hotel opened on the 1st of May and I am blessed to have been part of the first reception team of the hotel;

1st May 2017-20th September 2017 Reception/Spa Trainee

Fergus Style Pollensa Park & Spa, Port of Pollenca, Palma de Mallorca

Duties: Rotation between reception and spa reception;

Reception: Check-in and Check-out; assist guests at all time with any kind of request, question, concern or complaint they may have; check the future reservations in advance to prevent overbooking, exchange money and count the money from the cashier at the end of the shift, communicating in Spanish; **Spa**: Open and close the spa and all the facilities, present the spa and its facilities, make sure that everything is working properly, providing beach towels for the guests and swapping them daily, offering information about the spa's regulations, facilities and functions and making sure that they are respected and understood, taking massage appointments and manage the spa's revenue;

1st July 2016-15th September 2016

Night Audit

Vantage Deluxe Travel, MS River Discovery II, France

River boat travelling from Avignon to Chalon sur Saone and back, in 10- day cruises;

Duties: Working on the night shift at the boat's reception, making sure that safety and security of the guests and of the other crew members by doing a round the clock rotation of the boat, preparing the menu's for next day's meal and any other materials needed, after the embarkation day had to scan all the passports and save them according to the rooms the guests were staying in, before departure, I had to print out all the preliminary bills and to present them to the guests and to assist them with settling their payments and also allocate and prepare the room keys for the next arrival; assist any guest with their requests;

1st May 2015-1st June 2016 **Customer Support Agent**

CGS Romania, Bucharest, Romania

Duties: Working in the fraud detection and prevention department for an

American based phone company; we were checking online orders and making sure that the orders were placed correctly, delivered to the correct address and to the right customer and that the all the devices and services are paid on time;

1st March 2014-

Travel Agent

1st December 2014

Travel Associates Romania, Bucharest, Romania

Duties: checking and making orders for travel agencies in our online platform, providing and making sure that our customer's requests were fulfilled, confirming the order before the guests arrived to the property;